<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Ongoing Marketing</title>
    <link>https://blog.changworkshop.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Ongoing Marketing</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 08:28:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.changworkshop.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Vision Pro on Marketing</title>
      <link>https://blog.changworkshop.com/posts/vision-pro-on-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 08:28:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.changworkshop.com/posts/vision-pro-on-marketing/</guid>
      <description>What is Vision Pro In early June 2023, Apple has launched their new creative AR product which is called vision pro. According to the reaction of the industry , the product is undoubtedly beyond the expectation. On one hand it&amp;rsquo;s because to of the marketing strategy before its launch that Apple tried their best to pull down industry expectation. While on the other hand , vision pro does bring some features which are not predicted by the media worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Competitive Marketing in digital marketing era</title>
      <link>https://blog.changworkshop.com/posts/competitive-marketing-in-digital-marketing-era/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 04:09:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.changworkshop.com/posts/competitive-marketing-in-digital-marketing-era/</guid>
      <description>Typical case for competitive marketing When you are about to buy a mobile phone, which brand jumps out first in your mind? Apple iPhone is undoutedly the one leading the option list in the market. But what are the alternatives ? If you don&amp;rsquo;t have enough budget or you need an Android for a particular purpose, which brand are you thinking of right away when you are composing the list ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generative AI impact on  Online Advertisement</title>
      <link>https://blog.changworkshop.com/posts/generative-ai-online-advertisement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 16:46:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.changworkshop.com/posts/generative-ai-online-advertisement/</guid>
      <description>What is Generative AI ? The concept of Generative AI is hot from beginning of 2023. The technical industry becomes excited than ever before. The technical giants all around the world have started arm race on the generative AI products. Generative AI refers to the AI model that can be used to generate content based on what it has learned. It has begun to save work load dramatically in the daily r routine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Difficulty With Data</title>
      <link>https://blog.changworkshop.com/posts/difficulty-with-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 03:20:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.changworkshop.com/posts/difficulty-with-data/</guid>
      <description>What does data mean for marketing Along with the development of digital marketing, audience data becomes more critical for the campaigns. Nevertheless, how much can data help in the marketing campaigns ? No one can measure that so far like what was happening more than a century ago. Data plays a very sophisticated role in the online marketing for now, not only for marketers but also for the media providers/publishers as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Meta&#39;s Ambition with Metaverse</title>
      <link>https://blog.changworkshop.com/posts/why-metaverse/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 09:59:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.changworkshop.com/posts/why-metaverse/</guid>
      <description>What does Meta live with Meta which was previously called Facebook, is a traditional social media company. Facebook is obviously their product once shocking the world. It brought brandnew social communication approach to the public. However, as all the other internet companies, it had headache on how to monetize what they have. By checking Meta&amp;rsquo;s earning report of 2021 and 2022, Advertisement took 99% of it&amp;rsquo;s income. It seems internet industry can&amp;rsquo;t find a monetization solution better than advertisement.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
